onlineschooladmissions.com 2014-12-16

# Online School Admissions Privacy Policy

At www.onlineschooladmissions.com, we are committed to protect your privacy as a visitor or user of this website. The company does not sell, disseminate, disclose, trade, transmit, transfer, share, lease or rent any personally identifiable information to any third party unless and until it is specifically authorized by you. We follow strict guidelines and policies with regard to maintaining privacy of data or information we collect as declared in this privacy policy. 

**(a) Information we collect**

We collect your e-mail address, phone numbers, home address, location of city or town and the pin code and other personal information to serve you better. Whenever you use your account we keep records of your internet protocol address, the date and time of logging in and out on our website.  We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not share this information with anyone.  Registrant with whom we have an affiliate agreement may collect data for the purpose of gathering information, in order to assist you and to effect admissions more systematically & not for any commercial purposes.  
**  
A Note Regarding Children:**

Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use the Site unsupervised and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use this Site in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians.  
**  
(b) How We Use Information**  
We only use the e-mail address and the phone number of the registrants for the purpose of communication only. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in an unauthorized manner. We also provide you an opportunity to opt out or withdraw your account in case the registrant does not wish to share his personal information with us.     
**  
(c) Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on a visitor’s hard drive while they are visiting this website. We may utilize a short-lived form of cookie when you visit this site. At onlineschooladmissions.com, a cookie is only used to identify one unique visitor from another visitor during a particular session. A session is the period of active site-use while that unique visitor is linked to our server. We may use cookie technology during a session as a tool to carry forward your input information during enrolment or account registration process. This enables the visitor to effectively save time while he inputs his information on the website during the enrollment process. No personally identifiable information is stored on the cookie.  
**  
(d) Our Commitment to Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access and pilferage we maintain strict data confidentiality, and ensure the correct use of information. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We are not under any kind of obligation to share any information or data posted or shared with us by the user or the registrant with any third party whosoever.   
**  
(e) Third party links**  
This website contains links to third party websites that are not controlled by onlineschooladmissions.com. These third party links are made available to the user as a convenience and the user agrees to use these links at own risk. The company is not responsible for the any content or part of the content of the third party websites linked to the onlineschooladmissions.com or the company.  
**  
(f) Exceptions**  
Without prejudice to the clauses mentioned above company is authorized to share any information demanded by any authority or person in compliance with any law, rule, regulation, circular or direction issued by the Government of India, or of the State, or Union Territory or any other authority under the territory of India.       
**  
(g) Improving efficiency**  
You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site

You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, service offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications on the notification preferences page within your own personal profile. You may make changes to your notification preferences at any time.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Customer Support by mail at [support@onlineschooladmissions.com](mailto:support@onlineschooladmissions.com "support@onlineschooladmissions.com")
